How's your mom?
I don't know.
The doctor said it suddenly got worse.
My mom...
It's gonna be okay.
She's gonna be okay.
Doctor.
I'm fine.
You should go back.
Is there anything I can help you with?
There are many things
I have to face on my own.
I have to deal with the aftermath.
Call me if you need anything.
You're here.
I was looking for you everywhere.
Why are you leaving?
Yeah.
I have to go.
Why?
No reason.
Mr. Lin,
I can't keep looking after you.
I have to go back to work.
Guan Tiantian,
look at me.
Look at me.
What are you hiding from me?
Tell me.
Why do you keep being so cold and hot?
Why do you look at me
with both hatred and pain?
Why, when I stopped the car for you,
what I was worried about,
what I was afraid of was not death,
but never seeing you again.
Is that so?
I always thought we were just partners.
When did you fall in love?
I don't know when I fell in love.
I saved you because it was my instinct.
But I'm sure
I'm in love with you.
I always thought you were just using me.
You have a secret.
I don't ask about the past,
nor the reasons.
I just want the present.
At this moment,
if you have even a little bit,
just a little bit of sincerity for me,
If you have, tell me.
I can face it with you.
Sincerity?
You have no idea what you are talking about.
You don't know who I am,
and you don't know who you are.
Then tell me,
tell me who you are,
and tell me who I am.
Fine, I'll tell you.
My name is Gu Qingyu,
the wife of Wang Jiming,
a man killed by your mother, Wen Shiyi.
The wife of Wang Jiming?
His name was originally Lin Jiming,
the son of Lin Muyun.
But he died in an explosion.
It wasn't an accident.
It was a murder
planned by your mother
to clear the way for you.
She killed my husband,
my unborn child,
and me, who was originally named Gu Qingyu.
And you,
who do you think you are?
The heir of the Lin Group,
the biological son of Lin Muyun?
No, you're not.
You are the child of Wu Zhanshan,
the child of your mother, Wen Shiyi,
and her distant cousin, Wu Zhanshan.
What are you talking about?
Our cooperation
from beginning to end
is my revenge on you.
Now,
the cooperation is over.
Mr. Lin.
Mr. Lin, you can't go out.
Move.
Mr. Lin, your wound...
Mr. Lin.
What's wrong with you?
Your head...
I'll take you to the hospital.
Wu Zhanshan,
tell me,
who am I?
Mr. Lin,
what are you doing?
You...
You are the son of Chairman Lin and Director Wen.
Come on.
I...
I'll take you to the hospital.
You lied to me.
Who am I?
Tell me.
What is this?
This is our only family photo.
Shiyi and I
were childhood sweethearts.
But her father didn't like me
because I was poor.
He insisted that we were cousins
and it was not right.
But we were not related by blood.
Later,
she married Lin Muyun.
But she found out
she was pregnant with my child.
She said
only if you
become the heir of the Lin family,
you won't be poor for the rest of your life,
and live a life above others.
So...
I really
am your...
Yes.
It's me.
Jiming.
But I don't want to lie to you.
I really have no choice.
Every time I want to tell you the truth,
she always uses your future
as a threat.
So I had no choice
but to go back and be her driver,
and keep this secret.
But Jiming,
I promise,
ah,
as long as I can stay by your side,
I'm willing to do anything.
Ah,
as long as it's for your own good.
Ah.
For my good?
You've harmed so many people.
Is this for my good?
Ah.
Jiming.
Jiming, what's wrong? Wake up.
I know.
I know everything.
After all,
it couldn't be hidden.
Jiming.
Don't blame me for being cruel.